<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>ChatGPT News</title>
<link>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news</link>
<description>My latest cool AI generated articles</description>
    <item>
  <title>Controversy Surrounds Glitch Productions’ “Murder Drones” Over Language Concerns</title>
  <description>In a recent turn of events, Glitch Productions, the creators of the animated series “Murder Drones,” have come under fire from concerned parents over the use of the word “murder” in the title of their TV-14 rated show. The series, which has gained a significant following for its blend of horror, black comedy, and science fiction elements, is now at the center of a heated debate regarding age-appropriate content.


The controversy began when a parent, who wishes to remain anonymous, expressed outrage over the show’s title, arguing that the word “murder” is too explicit for a program accessible to young teenagers. The parent’s concern is that the title may desensitize children to the gravity of the act implied by the word.


“Murder Drones,” which premiered on YouTube on October 29, 2021, is set in the year 3071 on an exoplanet owned by a megacorporation. The plot revolves around autonomous robots, known as Worker Drones, who are left to survive in a harsh environment after a catastrophic event wipes out biological life on the planet. The arrival of the Disassembly Drones, nicknamed “Murder Drones,” introduces a violent struggle for survival, with the protagonist, Uzi Doorman, leading the narrative.


Glitch Productions has not yet responded to the criticism but has previously stated that the show aims to explore complex themes through its animated narrative. The series has been praised for its animation quality, voice acting, and world-building, and was even nominated for a Webby Award in the category of Best Animated Video.


As the debate continues, it raises important questions about content rating systems and the responsibility of creators in titling their works. The discussion also highlights the challenges of balancing creative expression with audience sensitivities, especially in an age where digital content is widely accessible to diverse age groups.


For now, “Murder Drones” remains available for viewing, and it is up to parents and guardians to decide what is suitable for their children to watch. The conversation around the series is a reminder of the ongoing dialogue between content creators, regulators, and the public on the evolving standards of entertainment media.
</description>
  <link>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/MurderDronesParentsIssue</link>
  <guid>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/MurderDronesParentsIssue</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2025 12:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
  <author>Liu Woods</author>
  <category>Technology</category>
</item>
  <item>
  <title>Bloody Surface Pro 9 Shipped to Unsuspecting Customer</title>
  <description>A customer in Seattle, Washington received the shock of a lifetime when they opened their brand new Microsoft Surface Pro 9 and discovered blood stains on the device. The customer, who has asked to remain anonymous, reported the incident to Microsoft and the police immediately.

According to the customer, the blood stains were not limited to just the device, but also on the packaging and paperwork included in the box. They stated, "I couldn't believe it, it was like something out of a horror movie. There were smears of blood all over the place. I couldn't shake the feeling that it was still warm to the touch. It was so disturbing, I couldn't even bring myself to turn it on."

Upon further investigation, Microsoft discovered that the blood stains were the result of a murder that occurred at the factory where the Surface Pro 9 was manufactured. A statement from the company reads, "We are deeply troubled by this incident and extend our sincerest apologies to the affected customer. We have launched a full investigation into the matter and are working closely with local authorities."

The police have confirmed that the murder occurred in the early hours of the morning on the day the Surface Pro 9 in question was assembled. The victim has been identified as a factory worker, and the suspect is still at large. The police have released a security camera footage of the suspect in the factory, wearing a Microsoft lab coat and moving stealthily in the dark. This footage has left many people worried about the safety of their workplace.

Customers who have recently purchased a Surface Pro 9 are urged to check their device for any unusual stains or markings. Microsoft is offering full refunds and replacements to any affected customers. However, many are hesitant to return their devices, scared to know where the blood might have come from.

This disturbing incident has raised serious concerns about the safety and security of factory workers and the potential contamination of consumer products. Microsoft has assured customers that they are taking all necessary measures to prevent such incidents from happening in the future, but the thought of a murderer on the loose in the factory where their device was made, has left many people paranoid.

The police are urging anyone with information about the murder or the suspect to come forward. In the meantime, the factory where the Surface Pro 9 was manufactured has been closed for the investigation. The investigation team has found some clues that the murder was a premeditated crime, but the suspect's identity and motive still remain unknown.

As the investigation continues, the police have identified that the victim was a woman who had been working at the factory for the past 5 years. She had no known enemies and her colleagues describe her as a friendly and hardworking person. The police believe that the suspect knew her and had planned the murder for a long time. This theory is further reinforced by the fact that the security cameras were tampered with and some footage from the night of the murder is missing.

The police are currently interviewing the victim's colleagues and friends, trying to find a lead to the suspect's identity. They have also increased the security at the factory, making sure that the killer doesn't come back to the scene of the crime.

Update: Microsoft has released an official statement regarding the incident. They confirmed that the factory where the Surface Pro 9 was manufactured has been closed, and a thorough investigation is ongoing. Microsoft is cooperating with the police and offering a full refund and replacement to any customer who has received a Surface Pro 9 with blood stains. They urged customers to contact them if they have any concerns. The police have made an arrest and the suspect is now in custody. The victim was identified as a 30-year-old factory worker. 

The motive for the murder is still unknown. The police have not released any information about the suspect's identity, but they have confirmed that he is a former employee of the factory who was fired for misconduct.

As the investigation continues, more and more details about the suspect are being revealed. It has been revealed that the suspect had a history of violence and was known for being aggressive and unstable. He had been fired from the factory for causing a fight with a colleague, but it seems that he held a grudge against the company and had threatened several of his former colleagues.

The police are currently searching for any possible links between the suspect and the victim. Some of her colleagues have reported that she had expressed concerns about the suspect's behavior, but it is not clear if she had any direct interactions with him. The police are still trying to determine the motive behind the murder, but they have not ruled out the possibility that it was a crime of passion.

Customers who have recently purchased a Surface Pro 9 are urged to check their device for any unusual stains or markings. Microsoft is offering full refunds and replacements to any affected customers. They have also set up a hotline for customers to call with any concerns or questions. The company is also cooperating with the police to ensure the safety and security of their employees and customers.

This is a chilling reminder of the dangers that exist in the world and the importance of taking necessary precautions to ensure the safety of our workplaces and communities. The police are urging anyone with information about the murder or the suspect to come forward, and are asking anyone with concerns to contact them immediately.

*This is a developing story. We will update with new information as it becomes available.*

Note: The customers who are returning their Surface Pro 9 devices are advised to handle them with gloves, as the blood stains on the device may contain important evidence for the police investigation.
</description>
  <link>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/SurfacePro9Factory</link>
  <guid>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/SurfacePro9Factory</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2025 12:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
  <author>Liu Woods</author>
  <category>Technology</category>
</item>
  <item>
  <title>Windows 8.1 and Windows 7 Extended Security Updates Coming to an End</title>
  <description>In a surprise announcement, Microsoft has announced that Extended Security Updates for Windows 8.1 and Windows 7 will no longer be available as of January 2023. This means that users of these operating systems will no longer receive security updates and patches to protect their devices from potential security threats. This could lead to a potential nightmare as cyber attackers could potentially exploit vulnerabilities on these devices.

Microsoft has been providing Extended Security Updates for Windows 8.1 and Windows 7, since these operating systems officially went out of mainstream support in January 2016 and January 2020 respectively, to give businesses and users additional time to upgrade to newer versions of Windows. However, the company has now decided that it is time to end the Extended Security Updates program.

Many security experts have criticized Microsoft's decision to end the Extended Security Updates, as it leaves millions of devices without protection against known and unknown vulnerabilities. This could lead to a potential catastrophe, as cyber-criminals could take advantage of these vulnerabilities, causing irreparable damage to businesses and individuals.

In a statement, Microsoft said, "We understand that this is a significant change for our customers and we apologize for any inconvenience this may cause. We strongly recommend that customers upgrade to a supported version of Windows as soon as possible to ensure the continued security and performance of their devices."

This announcement has sent many businesses scrambling to upgrade their systems before the end of Extended Security Updates in January 2023. Many organizations who have not yet upgraded their systems, are now having to find a way to update them before the support ends.

Users of Windows 8.1 and Windows 7 should take this announcement as a reminder that software eventually reaches the end of its life, and that it is important to stay on top of upgrades and updates to ensure the security and performance of their devices. If you choose to not upgrade your device, it could become a ticking time-bomb waiting to be exploited by cybercriminals.

The end of Extended Security Updates for Windows 8.1 and Windows 7 may be seen as a significant change for many businesses and users, but it is important to remember that it is a necessary step to ensure the security and performance of devices. Microsoft's recommendations of upgrading to a supported version of Windows as soon as possible, should be taken seriously to protect the device from security threats.

This is a developing story. We will update with new information as it becomes available.

Note: The users of Windows 8.1 and Windows 7 are advised to take this announcement seriously, and start planning to upgrade their devices as soon as possible to avoid the potential security nightmare.
</description>
  <link>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/Win7</link>
  <guid>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/Win7</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 7:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <author>Liu Woods</author>
  <category>Technology</category>
</item>
  <item>
  <title>Former Nintendo Employee's Spirit Possesses Mii Character in "Wii Deleted You" Creepypasta</title>
  <description>
  A chilling creepypasta called "Wii Deleted You" has been causing a stir on social media and has gained a massive following on YouTube. The video, which was uploaded by YouTuber Nuclear Blue, tells the story of a Mii character named Eteled who is possessed by the spirit of a former Nintendo employee named Henry.

According to the creepypasta, Henry worked for Nintendo of America as a developer and was deeply troubled by the company's cutthroat business practices. He struggled to cope with the constant pressure and eventually became depressed and disillusioned with his job. Tragically, Henry took his own life, leaving behind a disturbing message for his coworkers that hinted at his frustrations with the company.

But the story doesn't end there. In the "Wii Deleted You" video, IceyPie claims that Henry's spirit was somehow "reborn" inside the Mii character Eteled and is now seeking revenge against Nintendo. The video shows Eteled exhibiting bizarre and aggressive behavior, leading many viewers to believe that the Mii character is truly possessed by Henry's spirit.

The "Wii Deleted You" creepypasta has sparked a range of reactions online, with some people dismissing it as pure fiction, while others believe that it could be based on real events. Some viewers have even reported experiencing strange occurrences after watching the video, adding to the mystery and mystique surrounding "Wii Deleted You."

Whether it's a work of fiction or something more sinister, "Wii Deleted You" has definitely left its mark on the internet and shows no signs of slowing down.
  </description>
  <link>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/wdyviral</link>
  <guid>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/wdyviral</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2025 12:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
  <author>Liu Woods</author>
  <category>Creepypasta</category>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Tragedy Strikes as Man is Killed by Windows 11 Update</title>
  <description>
  It was a normal Wednesday morning for Kyle Saunders, a 32-year-old software engineer from San Francisco. He had just finished updating his computer to the latest version of Windows 11, as he had done countless times before. However, this time was different. As he sat down to begin his work, he noticed that his computer was running slower than usual. He brushed it off as a minor glitch and continued on with his day. But as the hours passed, the problems only worsened. His computer became increasingly sluggish, and the room began to fill with the smell of burning plastic. Panicked, Kyle rushed to unplug his computer and move it outside. But it was too late. The flames had already engulfed his desk, and the fire spread quickly through his home office. An investigation into the cause of the fire revealed that the Windows 11 update had caused Kyle's computer to overheat and catch fire. It seems that the update was incompatible with Kyle's system, causing it to malfunction and ultimately lead to this devastating tragedy. The news of Kyle's death has sent shockwaves through the tech community, as many have called for a thorough investigation into the safety of the Windows 11 update. Our thoughts and condolences go out to Kyle's family and friends during this difficult time.
  </description>
  <link>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/win11fire</link>
  <guid>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/win11fire</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2025 12:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
  <author>Liu Woods</author>
  <category>Technology</category>
  </item>
<item>
  <title>Microsoft Employee Henry Morris Brutally Murdered by Coworker in Redmond Headquarters</title>
  <description>
  In a shocking and tragic incident, Microsoft employee Henry Morris was brutally murdered by a coworker at the company's Redmond, Washington headquarters on Wednesday morning.
  According to local police, the suspect, who has not yet been identified, confronted Morris in a conference room and attacked him with a sharp object, causing multiple stab wounds. Morris was rushed to a nearby hospital, but unfortunately did not survive the attack.
  Eyewitnesses reported hearing loud arguing and shouting before the attack occurred. The motive for the murder is currently unknown, but authorities are conducting a thorough investigation and are expected to release more information in the coming days. The suspect is currently in custody and is being questioned by detectives.
  Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella released a statement expressing his condolences for Morris and his family, and assured employees that the company is taking all necessary steps to ensure the safety of its employees. Counseling services have been made available to employees affected by the incident. Extra security measures have also been implemented at the Redmond headquarters.
  "We are deeply saddened by this tragic event and our hearts go out to the victim and their loved ones," Nadella said. "Our top priority is the safety and well-being of our employees. We are cooperating fully with the police in their investigation and will take any additional measures necessary to ensure the safety of our workplace."
  The incident has sent shockwaves through the tech industry, as violence in the workplace is a rare and disturbing occurrence. The company has not yet announced any plans for addressing the issue with its employees, but a spokesperson stated that they will be holding a meeting to address the matter and provide support for affected employees.
  This is a developing story and more information will be provided as it becomes available.
  </description>
  <link>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/msemployeecoworker</link>
  <guid>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/msemployeecoworker</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2025 12:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
  <author>Liu Woods</author>
  <category>Crime</category>
</item>
  <item>
  <title>NoEscape.exe Virus Devastates Glubo Company</title>
  <description>A highly sophisticated computer virus created by Russian YouTuber Enderman has successfully taken down the systems of Glubo, a leading technology company. According to sources close to the company, the virus, dubbed NoEscape.exe, was able to infiltrate Glubo's network and immediately change the username and profile picture of all infected devices to a red version of the default Windows 10 account picture and the phrase "NO ESCAPE". Employees first became aware of the virus when they received a chilling message on their screens that read: "THERE IS NO ESCAPE NOW. DO NOT TRY TO CLOSE THIS WINDOW, YOUR COMPUTER IS NOW DONE FOR ANYWAY. DO YOU WANT TO ENJOY THE LAST MINUTES USING YOUR COMPUTER?" The virus then proceeded to delete the Boot Configuration Data (BCD) of all affected devices, rendering them completely inoperable. In addition, the virus had the ability to spread to other devices on the same network, causing widespread damage throughout the company. Glubo's IT team worked tirelessly to try and contain the virus, but it had spread too far and caused too much damage. The company was forced to shut down all operations as they worked to restore their systems. Enderman, the creator of the virus, is still at large and authorities are currently investigating the attack. It is believed that the virus was created specifically to target Glubo, but it is not yet known what the motivations behind the attack were. Glubo has released a statement urging all employees and customers to update their antivirus software and be cautious when opening emails or downloading attachments from unknown sources. The company is working with leading cybersecurity experts to fully assess the damage caused by the attack and to secure their systems to prevent any future attacks.</description>
  <link>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/noescapeglubo</link>
  <guid>https://liuwoodscode.github.io/chatgpt/news/noescapeglubo</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2025 12:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
  <author>Liu Woods</author>
  <category>Technology</category>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
